等着  我马上就到
Just wait in line. I'll be right there!
找到你了
有什么烧着了
Hey, something's burning.
哎  该死
Ow! Damn it.
离我的生日还有两个月呢吧
You know, my birthday isn't for another two months.
我知道
I know that.
我要是想的话可以给你做煎饼
I can make you pancakes if I want to.
不用了
I'm good.
别这样
Please don't do that.
是谁啊
Who's that?
你看见我的杯子了吗
Have you seen my mug?
带向日葵的那个
The one with the sunflowers on it.
你上学要钱吗
Do you need money for school?
我要迟到了
I'm gonna be late.
还是应该吃煎饼的
You should've gone for the pancakes.
这样她就满意了吗
And given her the satisfaction?
你从什么时候开始睡在沙发上的
So when'd you start sleeping on the couch?
不是  我只是经常在看电视的时候睡过去
No, I just keep on passing out in front of the TV.
我说的不是那个
I mean, not that I blame you.
她做的东西真他妈糟糕
Pretty shitty thing, what she did.
少说这种话
Hey, hey. None of that.
怎么了  打架了吗
So, what, you getting into fights now?
一群混蛋罢了
They were being assholes.
这不是理由
That's no excuse.
听着
Look...
我知道我和你妈之间的事
I know things between your mom and me--
和这个无关
Has nothing to do with this.
那其他孩子怎么样了
So how'd the other kid look?
另外两个孩子
The other two kids.
有一个哭了
One of them cried.
怎么了
Yeah?
是我
Hey, it's me.
我没想这么早叫你
I didn't want to wake you earlier.
有煎饼在
There are pancakes--
你打电话就为了这个吗
Is that why you're calling?
我其实也想聊聊天
Well, I also wanna talk.
我吃过了  回头见
I already ate. I'll see you later.
格雷格
Greg--
你他妈在逗我吗
Are you fucking kidding me?
天啊  康纳
Jesus Christ, Connor.
哈珀医生  您九点预约的病人到了
Dr. Harper, your nine o'clock is here.
贾斯汀·威特  十岁
Justin Whitter, 10 years old.
昨晚在诗人公园附近骑自行车时失踪
Went missing on a bike ride last night near Troubadour Park.
看公园的只找到了自行车  没找到人
Park ranger found the bike, no boy.
跟迈克尔·金一样啊
Just like Michael King?
不  我们不知道这两起事件之间的联系
No, we don't know if the two are connected.
迈克尔·金在骑车
Michael King was abducted
去城里的小店的时候被绑架了
cycling to a corner store in the city.
贾斯汀·威特  本地人  家境优越
Justin Whitter, local boy. Good home, respected family.
在县界线附近失踪
He went missing on county lines,
但是今天早上九点起
but as of nine o'clock this morning
这起案子归我们管了
the case was ruled ours.
斯皮茨知道了吗
Does Spitz know about this?
他想不想参与取决于他自己的意愿
It's up to him if he wants to get involved.
他会参与的
He'll wanna get involved.
你觉得合适的话我会让你带领这起案子的
I'll let you manage the situation as you see fit.
你负责这个了
You're lead on this.
明白
Got it.
康纳
Connor?
我只是个修窗户的  不会伤害你的
I'm just a window repairman. I'm not gonna hurt you.
-你在这干什么  -你丈夫打电话
- What are you doing here? - Your husband called
说有一个窗户坏了
about a broken window.
我刚给你换了个新的
Just finished putting in a new one for you.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
不用谢了
Okeydokey.
有什么问题再联系我就行了
Just give me a jingle if you have any problems with it,
再会
and have a good day.
谢谢你
Thank you.
不好意思  请问是谁让你进来的
I'm sorry, who let you in?
你的孩子  非常礼貌的一个小孩
That kid of yours. Very polite.
很有教养
You trained her well.
-谁  -是啊约翰  没有
- Who? - Yeah, John. No.
事实是  你找到的任何东西
And the truth is, anything you find
都可能是重要线索
could be important.
最后目击者称贾斯汀当时
Justin was last seen wearing a green soccer jersey
身着绿色足球衣  带着
and carrying--
我们很快就需要一些回复
Gonna want answers, and fast.
所以那个孩子是骑着车一个人穿过树林
So the kid's riding his bike all alone through the woods.
他的父母不介意吗
The parents are okay with that?
他十岁了  估计是觉得他已经够大了吧
He's 10. Figure he's old enough.
家庭生活怎么样  我真心问的
How's the home life? You know, really.
有爹有娘  两个孩子  生活美满
Mom, dad, two happy kids.
完美的美式家庭
Perfect all-American family.
是啊
Yeah.
这些不就够了吗
Aren't they all?
丽萨和我去年出了点问题
Lisa and I went through that rough patch last year.
别这样  斯皮茨
Hey, come on, Spitz.
听着
Look,
我也不是想装得什么都懂一样
I'm not saying I know anything.
不过之前有一个咨询师
Just there was this counselor.
杰姬就是个咨询师
Jackie is a counselor.
-是啊  -我们会没事的
- Yeah. - We'll be fine.
这儿有什么东西
There's something up here!
大家离开这里  你发现了什么
All right, step away. What you got?
天啊
Jesus Christ.
要当作证据吗
Sir, should we bring it in?
是  是的  你能
Yeah.Yeah, you can...
你可以把它包起来了
You can bag it.
谢谢  凯拉
Thanks, Kayla.
斯皮茨
Spitz.
你还好吗
You okay?
你还记得科尔·戈顿吗  在你之前
You remember Cole Gordon? It was before your time.
我当然记得
Oh, of course I remember.
那把绿色的小刀
The green knives.
和六个男孩
Six boys.
所有人都发现跟那个刀埋在一起
All found buried with those knives.
是啊  我知道
Yeah, I know.
但是戈顿他
But Gordon, he's--
没错  是我让他陷入那种境地的
Yeah, yeah, I helped put him there,
而且他也没能逃出来
and he ain't getting out.
所以你觉得呢
So what're you thinking?
能把酱递给我吗
Could you pass the dressing?
谢谢
Thank you.
今天我不在的时候
Hey, did you let a repairman in today
你是不是放了一个修理工进来了
when I wasn't here?
天啊  妈妈  就是那个人吗
Jesus, Mom, is that who it was?
你跟一个修理工出轨了吗
Did you screw a repairman?
好了
Okay.
你生气了
Okay, you're angry.
你怎么能这么做
How could you do that?
你怎么能这样对爸爸
How could you do that to Dad?
是谁
Who was it?
就是一个人  亲爱的
Just someone, sweetie--
别这么叫我
Oh, you don't get to call me that.
你以后都别想这么叫我了
You don't ever get to call me that again.
我知道你现在很生气
I see how mad you are.
你有什么资格这么镇定
You don't get to act like nothing happened!
做几个煎饼和一顿大餐就完事儿了吗
You think pancakes and fancy dinners are gonna make it up?
-不  我不是  -你毁了我们的家庭
- No, I don't-- - You ruined our family and
你他妈会付出代价的
you should fucking pay for it!
看到诗人公园现场的谢里尔
...the scene in Troubadour Park. Cheryl?
这个月内威特已经是失踪的第二个男孩了
Whitter is the second boy reported missing in the last month.
提醒一下各位  九岁的迈克尔·金
Now, if you remember, nine-year-old Michael King
就是在他家里
went missing just--
失踪的  专家们正告诫父母们
...from his house. Authorities are now telling parents of young
要看好小孩子们  并且要时刻监管
children to keep them close and well supervised at all times.
在早些时候的一场新闻发布会中
Earlier in a press conference,
警方负责人称他们一定能
the police chief said that he is confident...
将凶手绳之以
...that those who are responsible...
我都没听到你进来了
Oh, I didn't hear you pull in.
我给你打了好几个电话了
I tried calling you a bunch.
今天怎么样
How was your day?
你弄坏了个窗户吗
You broke a window?
我打电话上报了那个修理工
I called and reported that repairman they sent out.
他从我们家偷东西了
I think he stole from us.
什么
You what?
我们家所有的银器都没了
All of our silverware is completely gone.
找找抽屉里
Look in the drawer.
他还说了一些奇怪的话  什么帮忙的女孩
He said something strange about some girl who was helping--
他为什么要拿我们的银器呢
Why would he take our shitty silverware?
我也不知道  格雷格  但是我找不到
I don't know, Greg, but it's not there.
他的老板会调查的
His boss is gonna look into it.
我不知道你是怎么了
I don't know what's wrong with you.
跟我说说你的儿子吧  威特夫人
So tell us a little bit about your son, Mrs. Whitter.
他的名字叫贾斯汀  贾斯汀·威特
His name is Justin. Justin Whitter.
他十岁了
He's 10 years old.
他很高兴马上要上五年级了
Um... He's very excited about starting fifth grade.
他总是骑着车穿过大街小巷
He rides his bike all over this neighborhood all the time.
所以他放学骑车回家也很正常
So it's really normal for him to ride his bike home from school.
附近所有人都知道他
Everybody in the neighborhood knows him.
他是个好孩子
He's just a really great kid.
处方药  安比恩[安眠药]
嘿  你是怎么进来的
Hey. How'd you get in here?
过来
Come here.
你去哪啊
Where are you going?
来吧
Come on.
没错  这的确是你的房间
Yeah, this is your room, but,
等等  不是那里啊
no, not in there.
出来
Hey, come on.
出来吧
Come on.
我不会伤害你的
I'm not gonna hurt you.
康纳
Connor?
别这样  康纳
Connor, come on.
别无理取闹了  快让我出来
You're hilarious, but let me out now.
康纳
Connor?
康纳  快开门
Connor, open the door!
开门  我是认真的
Open the door. I'm serious!
康纳  快开门
Connor, open this door!
康纳
Connor!
你在干什么
What're you doing?
What are you doing?
我听到声音了  所以来看
I heard pounding, so I came up the--
康纳呢
Where's Connor?
他出去了
He's out.
什么
What?
有什么消息吗
Anything?
没有
No.
你想报警吗
Do you wanna call the station?
可能  我只是太累了吧
You know, maybe I'm just tired.
那你先上楼睡觉吧
Why don't you sleep upstairs tonight?
好  那我搬点东西去客房
Yeah, I'm gonna move some stuff into the guest room.
我知道你不会就这样原谅我
I know you can't just forgive me.
我不指望你能原谅  真的
I don't expect you to, I really don't.
但是我想让你知道  我什么都愿意  只要
But I want you to know I'll do whatever it takes to make--
你之前是真的想结婚吗
Did you wanna get married?
什么  什么意思
What? What do you mean?
一个不务正业的警察  赚不了几个钱
A shitty cop making shitty pay,
不仅在镇子上没什么人缘
this out-of-towner
你的父母也讨厌我
who your parents hated.
-我父母不讨厌你  -你爸爸讨厌我
- My parents didn't hate you. - Your dad hated me
因为他知道我没办法像他那样给你一切
'cause he knew I wouldn't provide for you like he did,
没法让你他妈住上间跟他家一样的大房子
like he did with this fucking house.
我从来没想要你给我荣华富贵
I never needed you to provide for me.
我从来没那样想过
I never wanted that.
但是我想
I wanted that.
你真的觉得
You really think
如果你没怀孕的话
we'd still be together
我们还会在一起吗
if you hadn't gotten pregnant?
我很高兴这份婚姻能走到今天
I'm glad things worked out the way they did.
我很努力了  格雷格
I'm trying, Greg.
屋顶上还有个男的  往上看  就在那
What about the guy on top? Watch it. Up there.
十一点钟方向  对  有掩体
Eleven o'clock. Yep. Covered.
别对着我开枪啊
Don't shoot me in the face!
我明白兄弟  我在掩护你
I know, man, I'm covering you!
就在那里  兄弟
Right there, right there, dude.
你在干嘛
What're you doing?
你刚去哪了
Where were you?
刚才有点口渴
I was thirsty.
都这么晚了  就别继续打游戏了吧
It's a little late to be playing video games, isn't it?
我明天送你上学
I'm taking you to school tomorrow.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
没什么  就是载你上学啊
Doesn't matter, I'm just taking you.
我又不会被绑架  妈
I'm not gonna get kidnapped, Mom.
我的天  我很久没有见过这个公仔了
Oh, my God, I haven't seen him in forever.
西皮  记得他吗
Hippie. Remember him?
不记得
No.
妈
Mom.
晚安
Good night.
戴维斯要见我们  现在过来
Davis wants to see us. Now.
好  我马上就到
Yeah, okay. I'll be right there.
抱歉
Sorry.
我错过了什么
What'd I miss?
科尔·戈顿
Cole Gordon.
以前的案子  半夜叫我起床就为了这个
A closed case. I got pulled out of bed for this.
你知道为什么叫你来  斯皮茨
You know why you're here, Spitz.
这人的作案手法和15年前你逮捕的
The MO is an exact match
一个连环儿童绑架案主犯高度相似
of a serial child abductor you put away 15 years ago.
你还在缩在被窝里的时候
I was on the phone
我就在和你的老搭档
with your old partner
通过电话了
while you were all tucked up.
他们送来了保存的资料
They sent what they still had on hand.
老天  把那些东西收起来
Jesus Christ. Put that shit away.
戈顿的辩护律师正在尝试
Gordon's defense attorney's trying to use it
利用这些证据申请无效审判
to build a case for a mistrial.
他们从不放过这些机会
They didn't waste any time.
我很遗憾要让那个白痴律师失望了
I'm sorry to disappoint the dickhead lawyer,
不过戈顿是一个被定罪的恋童癖
but Gordon was a convicted pedophile
当时在他车尾箱里查获了不胜数的刀子
with a trunk packed full of those knives,
更别说在他房子里
not to mention clothes from
发现了受害者当中
half a dozen of the victims
六个人的衣服
we found at his house.
这个人可能会是模仿犯罪
Yeah, well, it's probably a copycat.
不过我们要阻止他
But we need to get in front of this.
我已经派拉森去追查
I sent Larson to track down
那两个逃掉的男孩
the two boys that escaped,
布劳恩和特拉弗斯
Braun and Travers.
我的天
Oh, Jesus Christ.
虽然已经过去15年了
Yeah, it's been 15 years,
但他们可能还记得一些当时的细节
but they might remember details now
可以帮助戳穿戈顿的辩护
that could help impede Gordon's defense.
那我没错啊
I wasn't wrong.
当时我广泛和那些孩子都做过谈话
I interviewed both those boys extensively when it happened.
铁案如山  毫无疑问
There's no doubt. No doubt.
那你现在怎么
Then why'd you end up
还和我们坐在这儿呢  雷
with us, Ray?
给我们他的地址
Get his address.
但是他去监狱了  被关起来了
But he went to prison. He's locked away.
据我们最后的了解  确实如此
To the best of our knowledge he is,
布劳恩先生
Mr. Braun.
如果可以  我们想跟您儿子聊聊
But we'd like to talk to your son, if that's possible.
他在房子后面
He's out back.
汤米
Tommy.
Tommy?
有几个挺好的人想见你一面
There's some nice men here to see you.
汤米
Tommy?
记得我吗
Remember me?
斯皮茨基警官
Officer Spitzky.
好久不见了  汤米
It's been a long time, Tommy,
我还留着你送我的雷龙模型
but I still have that brontosaurus you gave me.
汤米
Tommy?
不  不  不  不  不
No, no, no, no, No, no, no, no!
不要  不要  不要
No! No! No!
不要  不要
No! No!
不要过来
No!
你好  汤米
Hey, Tommy.
汤米
Tommy?
你可以从头开始讲一遍吗
Can you start at the beginning for me?
我需要你回答一些问题  好吗
I need you to answer my questions, okay?
我知道你很害怕
I know you're scared.
是一个男的
There was a man.
一个男人吗
A man?
你认识他吗
Someone you knew?
不  不过他说他认识我们
No, but he said he knew us.
你是在哪里见到他的
Where did you see him?
他站在铁轨上看着我们
Watching us on the tracks.
是他弄伤了你的脸吗  汤米
Did he do that to your face, Tommy?
是我自己弄的
I did it to myself.
在我从那个树林里的木屋子出来以后
After the little house in the trees.
那就是他带你去的地方吗
Is that where he took you?
你能记起来那个屋子在哪吗
Do you think you can remember where it is?
已经不在那了
It's not there anymore.
那是个魔法屋  它消失了
It's a magic house. It disappears.
什么意思
What does that mean?
就是  你永远都找不到他了
It means... you're never gonna find him.
你好吗
Hey.
你怎么在这
What are you doing here?
我一早坐公交过来的
I took the bus out this morning.
我和我大学朋友住在布拉克斯福德
I'm staying with a college buddy in Braxfield.
你没收到我的短信吗
Did you not get my messages?
你不能在这  我儿子在家
You cannot be here. My son is here.
好吧  我们出去走走  今天放假
Well, let's go somewhere. Take the day off work.
-见到你真好  -不  先别这样
- It's so good to see you. - No, no, no, no.
你没看手机短信吗
Did you not get my texts?
-我上次说的话吓到你了吗  -没有
- Did I freak you out by what I said last time? - No, no.
-因为那时候是  -没有
- Because that was... - No, no.
完全不同的我
a whole different
因为我爱上你了
Because I'm in love with you!
我爱上你了  杰姬
I'm in love with you, Jackie.
我没法
I can't...
我不想和你在一起
I don't want to be with you.
杰姬  听着  我知道你很害怕
Jackie, listen. I know you're scared.
-托德  别说了  -我也害怕  但我们有
- Todd, stop! - I'm scared too. But what we have, you know--
我的天
Ow!Oh, my God.
怎么回事啊
Ow. What the hell?
-天啊  -让我看看
- Jesus. - Let me see.
没事  没事
No, no, I'm fine, I'm fine.
我还好  我要坐下来
I'm fine. I gotta sit down.
不  不  跟我来
No, no, come with me. Come with me.
亲爱的  我没事
Okay. All right, honey. I'm good.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
有没有搞错
What the fuck?
天啊
Oh, Jesus.
-杰姬  -小心
- Jackie. - Careful.
让我想起高中了  记得吗
This reminds me of high school. Remember?
总是溜进你爸妈的地下室
Sneaking into your parents' basement all those times.
-等等  -怎么了
- Wait, wait, wait, wait. - What? Okay.
这就像
Whoa. This is like...
过来这里
Come here.
-过来坐下  -我感觉有点疼
- Come here. - This kinda hurts a little bit.
-过来  -好了
- Come here. - Oh, nice, ohh.
太棒了
This is great. Yeah.
轻点
Be careful.
妈
Mom?
亲爱的  你要是做护士绝对行
Honey, you'd make an amazing nurse.
操  疼死我了
Oh, ow! Fuck.
等我送完康纳上学
As soon as Connor goes to school,
我就送你去医院
I think I should take you to the hospital.
听起来不错
Yeah, that sounds great.
你在打给我
You're calling me.
-你手机在哪  -你在说什么
- Where's your phone? - What're you talking about?
你手机呢
Where's your phone?
喂
Hello?
你手机放哪了吗
Did you leave your phone somewhere?
我的手机吗
My phone.
是你打开的吗
Did you turn this on?
没有
No.
你刚才在屋顶上吗
Were you just up on the roof?
什么  没有啊  你在说什么
What? No, what're you talking about?
你说要送我上学的
You said you were taking me to school.
是的
I am.
出什么事了吗
Is something wrong?
上车  我马上过去
Get in the car. I'll be right there.
康纳  你要是做了什么事
Connor, if you did something,
如果心里难受
if you were upset
你在说什么
What're you talking about?
你可以告诉我  我不会生气的
You can tell me. I won't be mad.
-我只希望…  -妈
- I just want... - Mom!
-很抱歉打扰您  哈珀女士  -不会
- Sorry to bother you, Mrs. Harper. - No,
威特女士  令郎的事让我很难过
Mrs. Whitter, I'm so sorry for your son
他有听说什么消息吗  您丈夫那边
Has he heard anything? Your husband?
我不知道
I-I... I'm not sure.
不过我知道他们正尽全力
I know they're doing everything they can.
我儿子就在外面某个地方
My son is out there somewhere.
他们会找到他的
They're gonna find him.
格雷格会找到他的
Greg is going to find him.
好
Yeah.
谢谢
Thanks.
你觉得他认识绑匪吗
You think he knew him?
什么
What?
贾斯汀·威特
Justin Whitter.
那孩子其实有可能认识绑匪
Chances are he knew the kidnapper.
有可能
Maybe.
不  你想想
No, think about it.
那孩子在骑车
Kid's on his bike.
看见犯人  他们互相认识
Sees the perp. They know each other.
所以那孩子停了下来
So the kids stops.
他把他带走
He grabs him,
扔下一把刀来甩掉我们
drops one of the knives to throw us off.
-斯皮茨  -可能吧
- Spitz? - Maybe.
或者
Or...
是他拦住了那个孩子
He stops the kid.
抱歉花了这么长时间  我原本…
Sorry it took so long, I didn't--
帮帮我
Help me.
天啊  杰姬  告诉我发生了什么
Jesus Christ, Jackie. Walk me through what happened.
-整件事  -我们聊了一会
- Everything. - We were talking.
就只聊天吗
Just talking?
对  我们在门口聊天
Yes, we were talking by the side of the house.
我明确拒绝了他
I explained that we were over,
然后不知道哪里掉下来这东西
and out of nowhere it just fell.
流了些血  不过不至于这样子
It was bleeding, but it wasn't like that.
为什么你不叫救护车
Why didn't you call an ambulance?
你能叫什么人来处理吗
Is there anyone you can call?
-你怎么没叫救护车  -是康纳干的
- Why didn't you call an ambulance? - It was Connor.
什么
What?
他在楼上
He was upstairs.
他那时很生气
He's been so angry.
很生气
So angry.
生气到想杀人吗
So angry he tried to kill someone.
-也许是个意外呢  -天呐  杰姬
- Maybe it was an accident? - Jesus Christ, Jackie.
我不知道发生了什么
I don't know what's happening--
不  不  你现在不能崩溃
No, no! You don't get to lose it right now!
听我说
Listen to me.
你知道如果真是儿子干的
Do you know...
他将面临什么吗
what will happen to our son?
我保不了他
I won't be able to protect him.
去把那些脏衣服换掉
Go change out of those clothes.
好
Okay.
对不起
I'm sorry.
对不起  对不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Sorry.
对不起
I'm sorry.
对不起  对不起  对不起
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你知道什么是蛙居吗
你是谁
蛙居
你知道什么是蛙居吗
这是谁
告诉我你是谁
杰姬
Jackie!
直接开车去医院  碰到什么都不要停下
Drive straight to the hospital. Don't stop for anything.
我上路再给你打电话
I'll call you when I'm on my way.
杰姬  我一定会找到他的
I'll find him, Jackie!
我一定会找到这个该死的混蛋的
I'm gonna find the son of a bitch who did this.
开车
Drive.
斯皮茨  911分局刚接到一个电话
Spitz. 911 dispatch just got a call from someone
来电者声称看到了绑匪
claiming to have seen our kidnapper.
不是吧  在哪儿
No shit. Where?
他们正在追踪定位信号
They're tracking GPS signal now.
哈珀还没接电话
And Harper's not answering his cell.
我直接去接他
I can pick him up.
你拍下来了吗
Did you get that on camera?
-拍了  -我以为没拍上呢  我离得太近了
- Yeah. - I thought that wasn't gonna happen. I was so close.
棒呆
Hell yeah!
天哪
Holy shit.
你看这视野
You see this view?
天哪
What?
我从没见过这么美的房子
I don't think I've ever seen a view this nice before.
这简直就是人间仙境
Nobody deserves this.
那是冰箱吗  这么高级
That's a fridge? What the hell?
别弄坏任何东西
Hey, don't break anything.
我没想碰坏东西
I wasn't planning on it.
我的天
My God!
他们竟然有  星战
They have "Battlestar"?
还有那么多酒
Look at all that wine.
这家一定都是酒鬼
Bet they're alcoholics.
天哪
Jesus.
他们照了这么多相片
They take so many pictures.
真是变态老妈
Creepy mom.
房子一直延伸
It just keeps going and going.
甚至还有配楼
It has, like, actual wings.
他们把你关起来了
They got you locked up.
亚历克
Alec!
快来看  我们有房间了
Hey, check it out. I found our room!
是客房哦  亲
Guest room, baby.
这才叫生活
This is the life.
这什么
What the...
床单上落满了灰尘
These sheets are covered in, like, a layer of dust.
他妈的像场沙尘暴一样  老天
It's a fucking sandstorm, Jesus.
这家人难道没有朋友吗
Do these people not have friends?
你不是说我们得睡在看不见的地方吗
Didn't you say we had to sleep somewhere out of sight?
我说过
I did.
跟我去咱们的卧室吧
Let me take you to our sleeping quarters.
到了晚上
And at night...
我们就睡在这里
we are going to sleep in here.
看
Ta-da.
你开玩笑吧
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
并没有
I'm not.
好吧
Okay.
所以说
So,
我现在应该讲讲
I should probably tell you a little bit about
我们到底在做什么
what we're doing.
这算是一部纪录片了  没错
So this is a documentary. Yeah.
我们将为你展现
It's to give you all a look
一名职业的蛙居党
at how a professional phrog
是如何进行蛙居的
goes about phrogging.
我们之所以被称为蛙居党
They call us phrogs with a "P-H"
因为我们从一家跳到另一家
because we hop from pad to pad
而房主却不知道我们的存在
undetected by the people who actually live in the house.
通常我在每一户停留不会超过
Usually I try to stay in a place for no longer than,
四五天
like, four or five days
这样不容易被户主发现
'cause it makes it harder to be discovered.
多数情况下  我尽可能不干扰
For the most part, I really try to disrupt
他们的生活
their lives as little as possible.
屋内最好有间客房
And it's a good thing that these people have a guest room.
我们要找的
That's what you wanna look for.
就是一间户主很少使用的房间
A room that is rarely used by the family
这可以做我们的根据地
that you can make headquarters.
正如你所见
As you can see,
我正在吃他们的食物
I'm eating some of their food.
这是可以的  因为
This is allowed because, you know,
女生天生就是吃货
a girl's gotta eat.
只要别吃掉太多就好
We just try not to take too much of one thing.
亚历克  你个混蛋
You asshole! Alec!
这个讨厌鬼是我的摄影师  亚历克
This disturbing creature is my cameraman, Alec.
真不明白你为啥要戴这么诡异的东西
I can't believe you brought this creepy thing with you.
怎么了  这很应景  我们是蛙居党呀
What? It's fitting. We're phrogs.
-这是个青蛙面具  -你个变态
- It's a frog. - You're such a freak.
他从没经历过蛙居  所以我在给他讲规矩
He has never done this before, so I'm showing him the ropes
而他则负责用他的小可爱相机记录下来
while he documents with his nifty camera.
我还让他挑选了这所房子
I also let him pick out this house.
我当然知道怎么挑选
And I sure know how to pick 'em, huh?
目前  一切正常
So far, so good.
现在是一天中最美好的时光
This is the best part of the day.
我们可以大声说话  房子现在全归我们
We get to be loud, and we have the house to ourselves
我们可以自由活动
and we can move about freely.
但当他们回家时
But when they come home,
我们只能躲进藏身之处
we have to stick to our hiding places
并保持安静
and stay quiet.
那时的感觉真心很烂
And that part's gonna suck.
没错
Yep.
那么
So...
现在是凌晨2点10分
It is ten minutes after 2:00 a.m.
亚历克和我刚睡着了
Alec and I fell asleep,
户主一定是在我们睡着时回家了
and the family must've come home while we were passed out.
你醒着吗  亚历克
Alec, are you awake?
亚历克  亚历克
Alec? Alec?
亚历克
Alec?
你在搞什么
What the hell are you doing?
我好无聊
I was bored.
你不能想什么时候出去就什么时候出去
You can't just go outside whenever you want.
他刚到家
He just got home.
谁
Who?
这家的丈夫
The husband.
他看见你了吗
Did he see you?
看到了  他挥了挥手
Yeah, I mean, he saw me. He waved.
好吧好吧  快点回来啦
Okay, very funny. Come on. Get back inside.
做个好梦
Sweet dreams.
好戏才刚刚开始
And here we go.
我们要迟到了
We're gonna be late.
你疯了吗
Hey, are you insane?
你难道想触发烟雾报警器吗
You trying to set off a smoke alarm?
-对啊  -离窗户远点
- Yes. - Stay away from the window.
天  谁能想到
God, who knew this phrogging thing
蛙居这么没劲
would give you such a stick up your ass?
嘘  轻声点
Shh! Hushed voices.
抱歉
Sorry.
老兄  你不知道这有多危险吗
Dude, I don't think you understand how dangerous this is.
我们会坐牢的
We could go to jail.
光是私闯民宅就够我们受的了
We're breaking so many laws just by being here.
我明白
I do understand.
但在被抓的边缘左右横跳不是最有趣的吗
But isn't that part of the fun, almost getting caught?
不  逃离被抓的边缘才是最有趣的
No, the fun is to not come close to getting caught.
想玩个文字游戏吗
Wanna play the word game?
好端端玩什么文字游戏
What is it with you and that word game?
找点事做而已
Something to fucking do.
好吧  是你一直缠着我要我跟来
Okay, you're the one who's been hounding me to come along.
我一个人本来挺开心的
I was perfectly happy doing this alone.
我知道
I know.
我很荣幸
I'm glad to.
我只是想更
I just thought it would be a little more...
有趣点
less shit.
这比地铁和
It's better than...
公园长椅好多了
...subways and park benches.
差不多
Just about.
好吧
Okay.
我想好一个
I'm thinking of a...
7个字母的词
seven-letter word.
B开头
It starts with a "B".
天哪  康纳
Jesus Christ, Connor.
王八蛋
Bastard.
你说什么
What?
你说的B开头7字词
Seven-letter word, starts with "B."
任务完成
Mission accomplished.
这里有多地方可以让我们藏东西
There's so many places to hide shit down there.
如果我们要跑  那是最佳路线
If we need a quick escape, that's our route.
来看看
Check it out.
你怎么做到的
How'd you do that?
我下载了个软件
Downloaded an app.
他家无线密码就写在任务表旁边
They keep their Wi-Fi password next to the chore chart.
你真是个鬼才
You are such a freak.
给他们捣捣乱不是会很有趣吗
Wouldn't it be kinda funny to mess with them?
随便拿点什么  让他们疑神疑鬼
Take some random shit, make them think they're going crazy?
不要
No.
这样不好
It wouldn't.
别再乱碰东西了  好吗
Stop touching stuff, okay?
你能想象这些人有多有钱吗
Can you believe how loaded these people are?
他们这么有钱  这就是他们要买的东西吗
They have so much money, and this is the shit they decide to buy?
我猜这家的妻子是个医生
The wife's some sort of doctor, I think.
她的信箱上写着
It was on her mail.
娇妻大夫
Dr. "Stepford Wife."
靠
Shit.
有人吗
Hello?
-有人打电话报修窗户吗  -稍等
- Someone call about a broken window? - Just a second!
让他进来  他不知道你不住这儿
Just let him in. He doesn't know you don't live here.
你好  我接到电话  说窗户坏了
Hi. I got a call about a broken window.
是的  我爸爸打的
Yeah, that was my dad.
就在这边
It's right this way.
亚历克  快来
Alec! Come on!
立刻
Now!
我只是个修窗户的  我不会伤害你的
I'm just a window repairman. I'm not gonna hurt you.
-你在这儿干什么  -你丈夫打电话
- What're you doing here? -Your husband
说窗户坏了
called about a broken window.
我刚给你换了个新的
Just finished putting in a new one.
不要再下楼了
No more going downstairs.
第五十九关
Ha-ha. Level 59.
去死吧  混蛋
Suck it, asshole.
这世道太乱了
This is so messed up.
又一个孩子失踪了
Another kid got swiped.
就在这  镇上
Here, in this town.
贾斯汀·威特  十岁
Justin Whitter. Ten years old.
噢对  贾斯汀
Oh, yeah, Justin.
你认识他吗
You know him?
不认识  明迪  我十岁时就不怎么跟
No, Mindy, I kinda stopped hanging out with ten-year-olds
那些十岁的小孩玩了
when I was, like, ten.
好了  你他妈激动什么
Okay, yeah. Fucking hysterical.
哥们  这真让人伤心
Dude, this is sad.
"失踪前穿着绿色足球衫
"Last seen wearing a green soccer jersey.
在诗人公园失踪"
Went missing in Troubadour Park."
他挺惨的
Sucks for him.
是的  是很惨
Yeah, it does.
你的水瓶
Here's your bottle.
好
Okay.
谢谢
Thanks.
你得多喝点水
Gotta stay hydrated.
谢了  老父亲
Thanks, Dad.
诗人公园案件  谢里尔
...the scene in Troubadour Park. Cheryl?
威特是过去一个月来失踪的第二个孩子
Whitter is the second boy reported missing in the last month.
他是个好孩子
He's just a really great kid.
过来
Come on.
这是你的房间  不过
Yeah, this is your room, but,
不  别进去
no, not in there.
过来
Hey, come on.
来吧
Come on.
我不会伤害你的
I'm not gonna hurt you.
康纳
Connor?
别这样  康纳
Connor, come on.
行了  你真调皮  让我出去
All right, you're hilarious, but let me out now.
康纳  我认真的  开门
Connor, I'm serious. Open the door.
康纳  开门
Connor, open the door!
开门
Open the door!
我认真的
I'm serious.
-康纳  开门  -格雷格
- Connor, open this door! - Greg?
康纳
Connor!
你在干什么
What're you doing?
What are you doing?
我听到撞击声  就上来
I heard pounding, so I came up the--
康纳在哪
Where's Connor?
他出去了
He's out.
什么
What?
在此处签名
帮忙带贾斯汀回家
亚历克
Alec!
赶快进来
Get back inside right now!
如果有人看见你了呢
What if someone sees you?
床怎么回事
What happened to the bed?
男主人尿床了
Husband pissed himself.
或者他是这么觉得的
Or so he thinks.
什么
What?
亚历克
Alec.
别啊  你答应过我的
Come on. You promised.
你说过你不会惹事的
You said that you would be cool.
我还没玩够呢
I'm not finished playing yet.
玩什么
Playing with what?
不  不  不该这样的
No. No. That's not how this works.
好吗  我们不捉弄这些人
Okay? We don't mess with these people.
我们不恐吓他们  我们只是共存
We don't terrorize them. We coexist.
那意义何在
Then what's the point?
如果我们不让他们质疑自己是否清醒
What's the point if we don't make them
那意义何在
question their sanity a little?
亲爱的  我上次说的事情吓到你了吗
Honey, did I freak you out by what I said last time?
我认真的
I mean it.
拜托  求你了
Come on, please.
我不想和你待在一起
I don't want to be with you.
行吧
Okeydokey.
什么
What the...
搞什么
What the hell?
让我看看
Let me see.
不  我没事  我没事
No, no, no, I'm fine. I'm fine.
我得坐下
I gotta sit down.
不  不  跟我来  跟我来
No, no, no, Come with me. Come with me.
-你他妈做了什么  -冷静  小问题而已
- What the fuck did you just do? - Relax. It's a little bump.
-你有什么毛病  -我没毛病
- What is wrong with you? - Nothing is wrong with me.
你知道他们会叫警察来吗
Do you realize that they're gonna call the cops?
-不  他们不会  -我们得从这出去
- No, they're not. - We have to get out of here.
是的  你去吧
Yeah, you do.
什么
What?
怎么回事
What is going on?
你为什么要这样  亚历克
Why are you doing this, Alec?
我带你到这来是因为信任你
Okay, I brought you here because I trusted you.
我知道
I know.
我很抱歉
And I'm sorry.
但我玩得很开心
But I'm having fun.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
怎么回事  亚历克  我不知道怎么了
What's going on? Alec, I don't know what's happening.
够了
That's it.
我们现在就走
We're leaving right now.
好吧
Okay.
该死
Shit.
我们的东西在地下室
Our stuff is in the basement.
-计划不错  -本来是不错的
- Great plan. - Well, it would've been.
我们得想办法让他们出房子
We need to figure out a way to get them out of the house
或者引开他们什么的
or just distract them or something.
他挂了电话
He dropped his phone.
是你打开的吗
Did you turn this on?
不是
No.
你刚才在屋顶上吗
Where you just up on the roof?
什么  没有啊  你在说什么
What? No, what're you talking about?
你说你要送我去学校的啊
You said you were taking me to school.
是的
I am.
上车  我马上过去
Get in the car. I'll be right there.
就知道在那里
Knew it was in there.
好样的
Good man.
该死
Holy shit.
很抱歉让你等这么久  我没有
So sorry it took so long, I wasn't--
你怎么不叫救护车
Why didn't you call an ambulance?
你就不能打电话给什么人吗
Is there anyone you can call?
-你怎么不叫救护车  -是康纳
- Why didn't you call an ambulance? - It was Connor.
-什么  -他在楼上
- What? - He was upstairs.
他一直很生气
He's been so angry.
生气到想杀人吗
So angry he tried to kill someone.
说不定只是个意外
Maybe it was an accident.
我不知道怎么了
I don't know what's happening.
不  不  你现在不能崩溃
No, no! You don't get to lose it right now!
听我说
Listen to me.
你知道  我们的儿子会怎么样吗
Do you know... what will happen to our son?
我会没法保护他
I won't be able to protect him.
亚历克
Alec?
出去
Get out.
别那么看着我
Don't look at me like that.
你疯了
You're insane.
-求你了  -我要报警了
- Please. - I'm calling the cops.
-不  我能让你毁了我这一切的  -放开我
- No, I am not going to let you ruin this for me. - Get off me!
明迪
Mindy?
快啊
Come on!
杰姬
Jackie!
我出发时打给你  我会找到他的  杰姬
I'll call you when I'm on my way. I'm gonna find him, Jackie.
我要找到那个对康纳下手的混蛋
I'm gonna find the son of a bitch who did this to Connor.
请接通  请接通
Please work, please work, please work.
-911  你有什么紧急情况  -我需要帮助
- 911, what's your emergency? - Hi. Yeah, I need help.
我觉得我和绑架那些男孩的人
I think I'm with the kidnapper...
在一起
of those boys.
我刚刚在他的车里醒来
I just woke up in his car.
女士  你在哪里
Ma'am, what location?
我不知道
I don't know.
-在吗  -我们在某个树林里
- Hello? - We're in the woods somewhere.
别挂电话  我们会用定位系统追踪你
Stay on the line. We'll track you on the GPS.
不  不  在吗
No, no. Hello?
能听见我吗
Hello, can you hear me?
-听得见吗  -听得见吗
- Hello? - Hello?
不  见鬼
No, shit!
别挂电话
Don't hang up.
救救我们  请救救我们
Help us! Help us, please!
他说他会杀了我们
He said he's gonna kill us!
快点  快点
Hurry! Hurry!
求你了  快点
Please, please hurry!
他在挖坑
He's digging a hole!
好了
Yeah.
求你了
Please!
我不会丢下你们的
I'm not gonna leave you.
快  快  他就在外面
Hurry. Hurry, he's out there!
-救救我们  -好了  我会把你们救出来的
- Help us! - Okay. I'm gonna get you out of here.
不  不
No. No.
会没事的
It's gonna be okay.
他回来了
He's back.
你不是说我们得在没人看见的地方睡觉吗
Didn't you say we had to sleep somewhere out of sight?
我是说过
I did.
我带你去睡觉的地方吧
Let me take you to our sleeping quarters.
晚上时
And at night...
混蛋
Son of a bitch.
斯皮茨
Spitz.
911调度中心刚刚接到电话
911 dispatch just got a call
有人说见到了绑架案的嫌犯
from someone claiming to have seen our kidnapper.
不会吧  哪里
No shit. Where?
醒醒
Wake up.
听着  听我说
Listen. Listen to me.
听我说
Listen to me.
我需要你
What I need you to do...
站起来
is stand up.
好吗
Okay?
站起来
Stand up.
好吗
Okay?
站起来就行
Just stand up.
站起来
Stand up.
求你了
Please...
你不必如此
You don't have to do this.
不  我必须这样
Yes, I do.
我知道你是谁
I know what you are.
那你是谁
And what are you?
某个义警吗
Some kind of vigilante?
我知道你带走了那些男孩
I know you took those boys.
不  是你带走了那些男孩
No, you took those boys.
你和你朋友绑架了那些男孩
You and your friend kidnapped those boys.
然后你来这恐吓这案子的首席警探
Then you came here to terrorize the lead detective on the case.
你绑了他的儿子
You tied up his son.
他就是下一个  我及时阻止了你
He was gonna be next. I stopped you just in time.
你朝我开枪  就是在朝一个警察开枪
You shoot me, you're shooting a cop.
你知道你会面临什么吗
You have any idea what's coming for you?
等等
Wait.
求你了
Please...
你不明白
You don't understand.
-我还小的时候  -我他妈不在乎
- When I was a little boy-- - I don't give a fuck.
斯皮茨基警探
Detective Spitzky?